Association for Research and Enlightenment Collection
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
- Publications, 1931 2015
  - Box 4A
    - The Searchlight, 1963; Folder 4A:8; McGuigan, Hilda C.; Brunelle, Genevieve; Carter, Mary Ellen; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; Clapp, Robert O.; Templeton, Clare; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Bramman, Ruth Hille; Turner, Albert E.; Adams, Frank; Cayce, Edgar Evans; -With Our Branches Lifted Upward: using the Edgar Cayce Readings while working with children - Hilda C. McGuigan -Feast...Or Famine? - Genevieve Brunelle, D.C. -Project Repeat: A Study of Early American History - Mary Ellen Carter -Full of Years - Juliet Brooke Ballard -Prayer - Juliet Brooke Ballard -Living the Truth: How the A.R.E. Study Groups Apply the Lessons in A Search for God - Robert O. Clapp -Atlantis in Mexico: An Interpretation of the Edgar Cayce records compared with current pre-Columbian research - Clare Templeton -The City Under The Sea - Juliet Brooke Ballard -When We Pray...extracts from 1962 Summer School Course on Prayer and Meditation - Hugh Lynn Cayce -The Prodigals - Ruth Hille Bramman -A Study of Color, Part I - Albert E. Turner -Do Ye Now Believe? - Frank O. Adams -The A.R.E. Research Program, Part II: The Remaining 37 Percent - Edgar Evans Cayce -A Study of Color, Part II: Albert E. Turner -Living the Truth, Part II - Robert O. Clapp
    - The Searchlight, 1964; Folder 4A:9; Mann, Alfred; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; Steinberger, Phyllis; Kasdin, Simon; Hardy, Marie; Cayce, Edgar Evans; Turner, Albert E.; Turner, Gladys Davis; McGarey, William; Smith, Enid Severy; -Science and the Readings - Alfred Mann -The Prophet - Juliet Brooke Ballard -A Study of Color, Part III: Color, Symbology, and Aura Charts - Phyllis Steinberger -Cabala: A Definition of Man - Simon Kasdin -Vocational Guidance from the Readings - Marie Hardy -Updating Earth Changes -Science Catches Up With A Psychic - Edgar Evans Cayce -There Is A Season: Balance As A Physical, Mental, and Spiritual Necessity - Juliet Brooke Ballard -The Shadow And The Sun - Juliet Brooke Ballard -Is Reincarnation In The Bible? Part III - Albert Turner -Edgar and Gertrude Cayce As I Knew Them - Gladys Davis Turner -Be Thou The Guide, Part I: A Commentary On Guidance In Dreams - William A. McGarey, M.D. -Attitudes and Emotions - Albert Turner -Gift of the Grotto - Enid Severy Smith
    - The Searchlight, 1965; Folder 4A:10; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; McGarey, William; Steinberger, Phyllis; Smith, Enid Severy; Adams, Frank; Mann, Alfred; Turner, Albert E.; Landers, Olive; Kasdin, Simon; Clapp, Robert O.; -The Meaning of the New Age - Hugh Lynn Cayce -The Day of the Lord - Juliet Brooke Ballard -Be Thou The Guide, Part II: Specific Guidance in Dreams - William A. McGarey -A Study of Color, Part III: Color, Symbology, and Aura Charts - Phyllis Steinberger -God in Nature - Juliet Brooke Ballard -Awake - Juliet Brooke Ballard -The Witnesses - Enid Severy Smith -Man and the Soil - Frank O. Adams -Dr. Velikovsky and Edgar Cayce - Alfred Mann -The Power of Sound - Juliet Brooke Ballard -The Word - Juliet Brooke Ballard -The Lost Tribes of Israel - Albert E. Turner -Know - And Change - Thyself! - Olive Landers -Ten Are The Numbers: based on the introduction to a book entitled The Esoteric Tarot - Simon Kasdin -The Promises of Jesus - Robert O. Clapp
    - Searchlight reprints, 1946 1965; Folder 4A:11
  - Box 4B
    - Diary-Letters, 1945 1947; Folder 4B:1-4B:4; Turner, Gladys Davis
    - Diary-Letters, 1948; Folder 4B:5; Allen, Eula
    - Newsletter from the Office, 1948; Folder 4B:6; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Chandler, Julia; Rice, Osca Austin
    - Association News, 1948; Folder 4B:7; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Rice, Osca Austin; Allen, Eula
    - Association News, 1949; Folder 4B:8; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Bonney, Marjorie
    - News from Headquarters, 1949; Folder 4B:9; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Davis, Louie I.; Sugrue, Thomas; Golden, Beth; Downey, Mary Elizabeth; Franco, Johan; Edmonds, Florence; Chandler, Julia
    - News from Headquarters, 1950; Folder 4B:10; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Bonney, Marjorie; Madigan, Jessica; Clairmonte, Nell; Rolf, Ida P.; Edmonds, Florence; Miller, Noah
    - News from Headquarters, 1951; Folder 4B:11; Johnson, Rudolph; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Mason, Frank Miller; Sechrist, Elsie; Bonney, Marjorie
    - News from Headquarters, 1952; Folder 4B:12; Bonney, Marjorie; Golden, Beth; Chandler, Julia; Gray, Lydia Schrader; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - News from Headquarters, supplement [Announcement of Edgar Cayce Readings Microfilming Project], 1951; Folder 4B:12; Johnson, Rudolph; Edmonds, Florence; Johnson, Douglas T.; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Sugrue, Thomas; Cayce, Edgar Evans; Turner, Gladys Davis
    - News from Headquarters, 1953; Folder 4B:13; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Clairmonte, Nell; Allen, Hildegarde; Reilly, Harold J.; Carter, Mary Ellen; Petersen, William; Schor, Robert; Godfrey, Helen; LeNoir, Ruth; White, Mildred; Gray, Lydia Schrader; Helms, Mignon
  - Box 5
    - News from Headquarters, 1954; Folder 5:1; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Helms, Mignon; White, Mildred; Godfrey, Helen; LeNoir, Ruth; Gray, Lydia Schrader; Warner, Nayan; Bonney, Marjorie; Newman, Almeda; Watson, Jean; Miller, Shane; Trim, Margaret G.; January 29, 1954 -Work on the Edgar Cayce Readings Under the Foundation Program -Activities Under the Association -Membership -Headquarters Operation -Publications -Lectures -Congress and Conferences -Group Study -Prayer Group -Experiments February 12, 1954 -Word of Thanks from Headquarters Committee -Attention Roanoke, Virginia -Boston Lecture -Searchlights -Saturday Evening Post story on reincarnation -Navy in Bermuda Being Reorganized (Hildegarde Allen in Bermuda) -Microfilm Viewer February 27, 1954 -Discover Yourself: Theme of the Twenty-Fourth Annual Congress -Boston Study Group -The Tape Recorded Libraries -You Will Survive Death (sermon by L.L. Dunnington of Iowa City, Iowa) -West Coast Conference Dates -The House Committee -February Visitors at Headquarters -Executive Committee Meeting Minutes (3/10/1954) -Two Surveys of Psychical Research: The Imprisoned Splendour by Raynor C. Johnson; Mysterious Psychic Phenomena by Hereward Carrington; Great Systems of Yoga by Ernest Wood; New World of the Mind by J.B. Rhine March 9, 1954 -letter from House Committee March 11, 1954 -Board of Trustees meeting on Summer School program -Congress Committee Meets -Open House and Musicale April 5, 1954 -West Coast Conferences -Summer School -House Committee Reports -June Congress -Music (HLC and Sally Cayce meeting with Beatrice and Richmond Seay to choose meditation music) April 22, 1954 -Cancer Abstract -Schedule of Weekly Activities at New York Center -Theron Helms obituary May 4, 1954 -HLC report of activities in Dallas, Texas -Recent Guests at Headquarters June 10, 1954 -Congress Lectures -The Project -Children's Play School -Congress Classes -Entertainment -What About the Western Trip? -1954 Congress Project outline June 30, 1954 -Congress report -Robert Schor update on extracts and Project seminar -William Price Searchlight article on Harold Reilly's Congress talk -Joseph Fiutko editing tape recordings -study of readings at Headquarters July 10, 1954 -Summer School Session -Tom Sugrue Memorial Library -Craig Healing Springs, Virginia -Headquarters Scene -Recent Additions to the Library July 15, 1954 -Thomas Sugrue Memorial Library mailing August 12, 1954 -Summer School now in session -Recreation -Scholarship -Administration Building -The Effectiveness of Prayer and Meditation -New York Center -Fishing Pier August 24, 1954 -Summer School report -Headquarters Scene -October Conference -Suggested Reading -Brother John Scripts -Recent Additions to the Library -Craig Healing Springs Prayer Laboratory as reported by Marjorie Bonney September 20, 1954 -October Conference -1954-55 New York Lecture Schedule -New Tapes Available -Where Were You at 12 o'Clock? (prayer for the ARE Administration Building Project) September 22, 1954 -letter from the House Committee October 4, 1954 -West Coast Conferences -Eastern Trip -October Conference -Former Membership Secretary Publishes Article on Edgar Cayce (Hildegarde Allen) November 5, 1954 -October conference report -San Francisco Conference -Esther Wynne and Hugh Lynn Cayce Return From October Trip -New York Activities December 13, 1954 -January Conference -Laboratory Class in Dream Analysis at the January Conference -Robert Schor Handles New York Classes -A Merry Christmas! -Book Notes (Edgar Cayce Publishing Co.)
    - News from Headquarters, 1955; Folder 5:2; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Davis, Louie I.; Bonney, Marjorie; Godfrey, Helen; Gray, Lydia Schrader; White, Mildred; LeNoir, Ruth; Helms, Mignon; Newman, Almeda; Johnson, Polly; Madigan, Jessica; Ashlock, Renee; Price, Jean; Carter, Mary Ellen; Warthman, Ellen M.; Watson, Eileen Margaret; January 10, 1955 -Membership update -January 1955 Conference -Manager's Western Spring Trip -Making Prayer Real -The January Conference schedule February 15, 1955 -House Committee -From Our Librarian February 25, 1955 -Membership Drive -Elsie Sechrist Lectures in Santa Monica -Special Tape Available (Mina Kerr on spiritual work in England and Scotland) -"That Old Gang of Mine" (Marjorie Bonney) -June 19-26 Set For 1955 Congress -Correction of Book Notes March 18, 1955 -House Committee letter on Edgar Cayce Birthday Celebration March 21, 1955 -Los Angeles events -"We See By The Papers..." April 11, 1955 -House Committee update -Report on January Conference -Second Summer School Session -Degravitation (U.S. military experiments) -Recent Visitors to Headquarters -Recent Books Added to the Library May 2, 1955 -Congress program -Evening Lectures -Class Discussion Leaders -Dallas / Fort Worth Conference May 16, 1955 -Los Angeles Conference report June 1, 1955 -Report on Conferences in San Jose and San Francisco -House Committee Appreciates Cooperation -Magazine Articles on Edgar Cayce -The Dead Sea Scrolls Parallel the Readings -June Congress -Lydia Schrader Gray's Apartment June 15, 1955 -Congress theme: Your Bible and You -California Lectures -United Nations Meditation Room -New Tape Available -Manager Takes July Vacation -Headquarters Scene -Recent Books Added to the Library June 24, 1955 -report on June Congress -A Project Within the Congress Week July 19, 1955 -Orion Magazine -Astrology Guide -Announcing a New Service for Members (index sheets) -Manager on Camping Trip With Family Sends Postcards to A.R.E. -Bring Your Children to the Summer Session August 30, 1955 -Headquarters updates -lectures in California -Summer School session comments October 5, 1955 -New York Lecture Series -California Activities -Washington, D.C. -Christmas Booklet -October Conference schedule November 7, 1955 -October Conference -California Activity -New York Lecture -Group Work in the Central Lake Region -Many Mansions Gets Around -Searchlights December 7, 1955 -January 1956 conference: Psychic Energy through the Endocrine Glands -New York Activity -California Activity -Anti-Gravity
    - News from Headquarters, 1956; Folder 5:3; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Godfrey, Helen; Helms, Mignon; Gray, Lydia Schrader; White, Mildred; LeNoir, Ruth; Newman, Almeda; Gammon, Margaret; Ashlock, Renee; Huffman, Grace; Wynne, Esther; Carter, Mary Ellen; Warner, Nayan; Adriance, Robert; Bonney, Marjorie; January 10, 1956 -lecture by Cyril C. Richardson on Paranormal Healing in History and Modern Practice -Shane Miller classes on Working with Dreams as Recommended by the Edgar Cayce Readings -California Activity -January Conference schedule -Selections from the Edgar Cayce Readings: Descriptions of Gland-Functions January 25, 1956 -letter from House Committee February 4, 1956 -Headquarters updates -Doings in New York -Washington Members, Mark Your Calendars -What's Cookin' in California? -Sales Booming! (The Search for Bridey Murphy, book by Morey Bernstein) -Dates Set for June Congress and the Summer School Sessions -A Book of Extracts from the Readings -Edgar Cayce in "Chimes" Magazine March 3, 1956 -Florence Edmonds obituary -New York Center schedule of events -California Activity -Dates for California Conferences Set April 1, 1956 -move from 308 Arctic Circle to 67th Street and Atlantic -New York Activity -San Francisco Activity -Schedule of Lydia Schrader Gray's and Esther Wynne's Trip -Schedule of Hugh Lynn Cayce's Trip April 21, 1956 -announcement of move to original Hospital Building; cost of supplies and furnishings -The Edgar Cayce Memorial Foundation brochure of renovated Hospital building May 1, 1956 -Dallas Conference -Cleveland Activity -New York Activity -Association Headquarters -June 1956 Congress -August 1956 Summer School June 9, 1956 -Congress update -Progress on Headquarters -1956 Summer School -Esther Wynne and Lydia Gray -Have You Heard? (There Is A River in paperback by Dell publishing; Edgar Cayce pamphlet by Fawcett Publishing; The Bridey Murphy Story filming in Virginia Beach) -New Letterhead June 19, 1956 -Tuesday Study Group Meeting on Search for God June 1956 -Index of Extracts from the Edgar Cayce Readings July 15, 1956 -The Twenty-Fifth Annual Congress -Headquarters Scene -Post Scripts -explanation of and update on The Edgar Cayce Readings indexing and microfilming project August 1, 1956 -Board of Trustees semi-annual meeting -Trustees -Officers -Membership Changes -Publishing Company Stock to be Purchased by Association -Summer School -New Publications -Bridey Murphy Picture -Reports (Lydia Gray, Esther Wynne, Lucille Kahn, Nell Clairmonte -Headquarters Scene booklet, Third Summer Session of a New School for the Expansion of Consciousness October 8, 1956 -Progress Report on the Building October 12, 1956 -HLC tour update -October conference -New York -California -Juicy Item #894 (membership dues) -Books (There Is A River paperback; Mystery Man of Miracles by Joseph Millard) -Juicy Item #895 (gift of California dates from Renee' Ashlock) November 10, 1956 -Notes on the Headquarters Scene -Contributions to the Improvement of Headquarters Department -The Widening Circle (East Coast events) -Memo from the Business Manager December 5, 1956 -Sunday afternoon forum series -January Conference -Library Fund -Note from Business Manager (Bob Adriance) -Monthly Selections from the EC Readings -Beth Golden obituary
    - News from Headquarters, 1957; Folder 5:4; Warner, Nayan; Bonney, Marjorie; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Perry, Dorothy; Adriance, Robert; Carter, Mary Ellen; January 11, 1957 -Notes on the Headquarters Scene -Edgar Cayce's Birthday Party -Reports We Like to Pass Along -January Conference schedule February 4, 1957 -The World Within (book by Gina Cerminara) -West-of-the- Mississippi Conferences -June Congress -January Conference -Los Angeles -New York March 1, 1957 -Correction (article on Radio Active and Wet Cell appliances) -Animated Ash -New York City -The Bells Are Ringing (marriage of Jeanne Goodell and Peter Schultz) -Retreat (prayer at Headquarters) -Edgar Cayce's Birthday -Hugh Lynn's Lecture Schedule April 1, 1957 -HLC West Coast Trip -Eight Monday evening classes on The Philosophy of the Edgar Cayce Readings -March selections for sponsoring members -Prayer Group retreat -June Congress -August Summer School April 1957 -Edgar Cayce Publishing Company order form May 1, 1957 -HLC tour report -Dr. Dryden L. Phelps Will Speak at June Congress -Membership - Contributions - Book Orders -New Study Group Activity -Library Books -Hugh Lynn Cayce - May Itinerary June 1, 1957 -new buzzers on Headquarters doors -Library -Individual Reference File -Tape Library -Planetary Sojourns (May selections to Sponsoring Members) -New Study Groups - Denver, Colorado -Phoenix, Arizona; Houston, Texas -Membership - Contributions - Book Orders -New Staff Member: Joe Flanagan for EC Publishing Company -Coming "World Changes" (Within Headquarters) June 26, 1957 -Study-Prayer Groups Program July 5, 1957 -June Congress report -Summer School -Bookkeeping Help -Book Reviews -Attention Long Beach, California -Reincarnation (Fred Keziah charts) -Child Training August 3,1957 -Summer School report -Handicraft Classes -Summer School Project -Gerald Heard Lecture -October Congress -Hugh Lynn Cayce lecture in Washington, D.C. -Gina Cerminara lecture series -Reminder RE Money Sent In August 9, 1957 -Impressions of new Headquarters from new staff member (Dorothy Perry) -Library -Meditation Room -Dining Room (Salad Bowl) -Book Room -Library -New Publishing Program Gathers Speed -Study Groups -Summer School -Work Project -Annie Cayce obituary program, Fourth Summer Session of a New School for the Expansion of Consciousness EC Publishing Company Order Form, September 1957 October 5, 1957 -Esther Wynne Mid-West tour -Attention California -Gerald Heard Lectures -Sponsoring Members Selections -Reservations at Headquarters -October 1957 conference schedule November 5, 1957 -The Edgar Cayce Phenomenon booklet -The American Mercury -Esther Wynne speaking tour -Headquarters Scene -Notes from the Business Manager December 10, 1957 -January Conference -Gina Cerminara's World -Introductory Booklet -Julia Chandler to Lecture -Esther Wynne to Lecture -New Book List -A.R.E. financial report to members
    - News from Headquarters, 1958; Folder 5:5; Bonney, Marjorie; April 23, 1958 -Opportunity for LIMITED number of members to finance summer season at Association working in the SALAD BOWL A.R.E. Summer School 1958 Book List for Class Related to the Gurdijeff-Ouspensky Ideas Sponsoring Member Ballot for nomination of new trustees - June 1958
    - News from Headquarters, supplement [Statement of Policy as to External Publication of the Edgar Cayce Readings by Individuals], 1958; Folder 5:6
    - A.R.E. News, 1966; Folder 5:7; Landers, Olive; January 1966 -Introducing the A.R.E. News -An Important Committee (Washington) -Coming Tour of Great Britain -Laboratory Evidence for the Healing Effects of Laying on of Hands -Glimpses of Recent Visitors to Virginia Beach Headquarters -Bay Area Lectures -Col. Adams and his Course on Edgar Cayce -Dallas Prayer Retreat -Sunday Forum Lectures -November 1965 Progress Report Edgar Cayce Foundation -Study Group News -Searchlight Editor Resigns (Mary Ellen Carter) -A New Find (Seabeck Conference Grounds) -Robert A. Adriance Member Executive Committee -ARE Library News -A Fitting Memorial (Ida May Wilcox [Mrs. William Price]) February, 1966 -New Building Under Construction (Esther Wynne building extension) -Our Newest Product (A.R.E. Journal) -The Cleveland Council -December 1965 Progress Report Edgar Cayce Foundatino -Study Group News -Sunday Forum Speakers at VA Beach Headquarters (Harold Reilly, Dorothy Evelyn Stanley, Ray Hanchey) -Eula (Mrs. Harold G.) Allen member of the A.R.E. Executive Committee -ARE Library News -Notes from Washington, D.C. March, 1966 -Camp Plans Take Shape -Study Group News -January 1966 Progress Report Edgar Cayce Foundation -New ARE Booklets -Sunday Forum Speakers at VA Beach Headquarters (HLC, Lewis Foster) -Television Exposure -Trip to Israel -Daily Peace Effort -Ruben Miller, Member of ARE Executive Committee -ARE Library News -Students Favor There Is A River April, 1966 -Expansion of ARE Healing Prayer Program and its Leaders (Ruth LeNoir, Mrs. Lyttleton W. Ballard (Juliet Brooke), Mary Ann Woodward -How to Participate in the Prayer Program -February 1966 Progress Report Edgar Cayce Foundation -Canadian Chosen Camp Director (Erik Englebert) -Study Group News -Jess Stearn in residence -Murray Main, Member of ARE Executive Committee -Meditation Retreat (Riley Simmons) -A World-Wide Headliner Coming Here (Marcus Bach) -Col. Adams in England -ARE Library News May, 1966 -A Most Exciting Expedition (ARE Trip to Israel) -In Memoriam (Julia Chandler) -March 1966 Progress Report Edgar Cayce Foundation -Dallas, Texas ARE Council -Elsie Sechrist Lecturing in London -High School Essay Contest -Ray Hanchey, Member ARE Executive Committee -Weekly Prayer Period Instituted -The Popular Paperback (There Is A River) -ARE Library News -Col. Adams in England -Study Group News -Camp Fund Progress Report -Work begins on the press wing roof June, 1966 -Worralls Replace Henard on S.F.F. - A.R.E. Leadership Program -Nell Clairmonte at Congress -Virginia Beach Spring Conference -The San Francisco Bay Area Council -April 1966 Progress Report Edgar Cayce Foundation -Congress Speaker (Lucille Kahn) -New York Spring Conference -Prayer Period Notice -ARE Camp News -ARE Midwest Conference -Study Group News -ARE Library News -The Sleeping Prophet (Jess Stearn) -Col. Adams in England -Eula Allen in Washington, D.C. -Austin Rice Lectures in Florida July, 1966 -From Coast to Coast - ARE Your Host! -ARE - Free Attraction -All Aboard for Asilomar -San Francisco Conference -ARE Southwest Headquarters Spring Conference -May 1966 Progress Report Edgar Cayce Foundation -Modesto-Stockton Workshop -San Francisco Bay Area Council Notice -Northwest Conference -Cancellation (Jeane Dixon) -Beach Offers Summer Scholarships -Dr. Bro on New York TV -ARE on Television in Norfolk -Dr. Charles T. Tart Will Lecture -Psychiatrist Presents Evidence of Reincarnation (Dr. Ian Stevenson) -You Are Forever (book by Eula Allen) -Study Group News -Col. Adams in England August, 1966 -Prospective Edgar Cayce Memorial Library - Foundation Building -A 'PSI' Experiment Open to All (Luther Meyer) -June 1966 Progress Report Edgar Cayce Foundation -New Search for Atlantis -Leading ARE Member Winner in Political Election (Dr. Irene Hickman) -Scenes in the New Press Building -Study Group News -Paper on Parapsychology (Frederick Dommeyer) -New Quarters in New York -Fall Conference -ARE Trustees Newly Elected -New Coordinator for Headquarters (Helen Reeve) -Dr. Harold Reilly Gives Therapy Course at Virginia Beach Summer School -ARE Library News -ARE Group in the Netherlands September, 1966 -Fall Conference at Virginia Beach Headquarters - October 9-15 -Impressions of a Visitor from Afar (Maurice Mindle, London, England) -Nuggets to Note -Reverberations of Summer Activities at Virginia Beach Headquarters -Study Group News -Summer Retrospect -Did You Forget? (Lost and Found) -Take a Look at the ARE Press -Camp Clips October, 1966 -Fall Conference at Virginia Beach: The Covenant Community -ARE Camp Expands -New York City Fall Conference -More New York News -More Merrymaking -ARE Camp Views -Study Group News -In Memoriam (Peter Ballbusch) -Attention Program Planners (William and Fonchen Lord) -ARE Library News -Lecturing on Edgar Cayce (Margaret Holtman) November, 1966 -Clinic-To-Be at A.R.E. (Harold J. Reilly) -New Staff Member (Jeffrey Furst) -Los Angeles Council -England Again Next Year (Col. Frank Adams) -Psychedelic Seminar Held in New York -Echoes of the Virginia Beach Fall Conference -Study Group News -ARE Group Candidates -Fall Celebration in Dallas -Visiting Members -ARE Library News December, 1966 -A Weekend with Marcus Bach and the Edgar Cayce Readings! -Sunday Forum Prospects -Summer Activity Program, 1967, at Virginia Beach Headquarters -Lectures and Lecturers Here and There -In New York (Nell Clairmonte) -She Never Thinks "Old" (Elizabeth Milholland) -A Forward-Looking Group (organic food group) -Texas 1967 Conference) -Study Group News -News Nuggets -ARE Library News -Announcement (booklet by Swami Radha of the Yasodhara Ashram, British Columbia) -What Dream Category Does This Fall Under? (Mary Lou Eades dream about HLC) -Using the Readings (Audrey Mason)